Hello
Привет
Now the funny situation was
Сейчас сейчас смешная ситуация была
very very
очень очень
two guys from Greenland but they apparently
двое ребят с Гренландии но они видимо
immediately saw that the Russian flag and but they are
сразу видели что Российский флаг и но
kidding, that is, they
прикалываются то есть по-английски
speak English and are kidding
говорят и прикалываются
Well, I taught them new Russian words I
Ну я их научил новым словам русским
went to
Пошел
say goodbye, I don’t know English, but
попрощаюсь я английский то не знаю но
I’m a programmer  I know
смысле как я программист Я знаю
English only technically,
английский только технически
that is, I practically don’t know spoken English,
то есть разговорного практически не знаю
so we
так
talked somehow
кое как пообщались
Well, the guys from Greenland threw
Ну вот ребятам с Гренландии подкинул
new Russian words
новые русские слова
to laugh when
смеяться когда
you
вам
Ukrainians laugh only a
украинцев смеяться только
funny moment
смешной момент
a funny moment was that they
смешной момент был тем что они меня
met me with Russian words
встретили словами русскими
funny someone had already taught them before  That
смешной кто-то их уже научил до этого
is, if I am with Russian Russians, it
То есть если я буду с русскими русскими
will be funny to you.
вам будет смешно да Ну да почему нет
I communicate with Ukrainians and quite
два с украинцами общаюсь и достаточно
often getting on children Well, basically they are
часто попадая на детей Ну в основном это
boys
пацаны
and now they have a reaction right away, that is, it just
и вот у них реакция сразу же вот то есть
turns on immediately starts swearing
только включается сразу начинается маты
at mother and swearing at mother damn it,
мат на мать и мат на мать блин
trying to try to communicate normally with them is
пытаешься пытаешься с ними нормально
useless How do you raise
общаться бесполезно Как вы воспитываете
children to See the case  in that, as it were,
детей до Смотрите дело в том что как бы
this is a very correct reaction. children. They are
это очень правильная реакция дети Они
honest. They are open. For example, I also want
честные Они открыты Например я тоже хочу
to send you, but no matter how I try, I
вас послать но как бы я стараюсь я
put on a mask of decency and start
надеваю маску приличие так и начинаю
smiling in order to at least talk a little. the
улыбаться для того чтобы хоть немножко
children don’t have this, let’s say,
поговорили у детей нету вот этой скажем
pretense. children. They understand that  here
наигранности дети Они понимают что вот
you are an [ __ ] from Russia they immediately send you Well,
вы [__] из России сразу посылают вас Ну
it’s normal
это же нормально
for children to kill their parents, firstly,
у детей убивают родителей во-первых
see what we say As they say,
смотрите то что допустим Как говорится
you saw the flag of Russia that I’m from Russia, you
вы увидели флажок России что я с России
never know Maybe I went through BP through
мало ли Может я через BP зашёл через
Russian
российский
secondly
во-вторых
Why am I an [ __ ] The thing is  the fact that we have
Почему я [__] Дело в том что у нас в
a lot of people in Russia who support Ukraine,
России много кто поддерживает Украину
I’ll tell you why the [ __ ], look because
я вам скажу почему [__] смотри потому
you’ve been on chat roulette for two years and
что вы два года вылазите в чат рулетку и
you have some claims against Ukrainian
у вас какие-то претензии к украинским
children you don’t have claims against Russia
детям у вас нет претензии к России
you start How do you bring them up there and
вы начинаете Как вы их там воспитывать и
so  further, that is, you have no questions for
так дальше то есть у вас нет вопросов к
Russian adults. What the hell are they
российским взрослым Какого хрена они
killing these little children in Ukraine, and
убивают этих маленьких детей в Украине а
little children have little children in
у маленьких детей маленьким детям в
Ukraine, you have such
Украине у вас у этого она такое есть
questions for some reason, it’s interesting,
вопросы почему-то интересно
well, how did you kill young children for eight years
хорошо а как вы восемь лет убивали
?  I say that the children They immediately
Я же вам говорю что дети Они сразу
say I still have to smile and
говорят я еще должен улыбаться и
talk with you for five minutes, for example,
поговорить с вами пять минут например
how is it done And the children right away you are an [ __ ]
там как делается А дети сразу вы [__]
They don’t need these people
Им не нужно этих людей я пять
they started a war there, they waged their own
тем что начали там войну вели свои
armed forces of Russia,
вооруженные силы России там не было 14
grandpa was not there for 14 years Who was
года дедуля Кто там был
who And who is the shooter
кто А кто такой стрелков
shooter [ __ ] Why 100 look he is the
стрелков [__] Почему 100 смотрите он
first minister of defense of some Donetsk
первый министр обороны какой-то Донецкой
People's Republic And who was the first
народной Республики А кто был первым
head of the Donetsk People's Republic
главой Донецкой народной Республики
Tell me again I say  the shooters are
Подскажите мне еще раз говорю стрелков
[ __ ],
мудила
like you, you are all [ __ ] there, I say
как и ты вы все мудилы там я говорю дети
our children are rummaging about who was the first head of the
у нас шарят это кто был первым главой
Donetsk People's Republic How do I
Донецкой народной Республики Я откуда
know
знаю
your current deputy Yes Moskvich
ваш теперешний депутат Да Москвич
Borodai citizen of the Russian Federation
бородай гражданин Российской Федерации
Minister of Defense of the Donetsk Republic
министр обороны Донецкой Республики тоже
was also a shooter Moskvich citizen of the
был стрелков Москвич гражданин
Russian Federation
Российской Федерации
Ministry of Internal Affairs of the Donetsk People's Republic
МВД Донецкой народной Республики
Muscovites came to the Russian Federation,
Российской Федерации приехали москвичи
created some kind of DPR, captured
создали какой-то ДНР по захватывали тут
cities here and says that there is no Russia here
города и рассказывает что тут России нет
We have some kind of war here for you children,
У нас тут какая-то война вам дети
which is why they say that you are [ __ ] And what
поэтому и говорят что вы [__] А что им
else do they need to say if you have never understood for 8 years
еще надо говорить если вы 8 лет никогда
9 years already  Yes, that your country
не поняли 9 лет уже да что ваша страна
is killing these children in our country and you are
убивает этих детей в нашей стране и вы
still coming out Yes, and you don’t understand Why
еще выходите Да и не понимаете Почему
the children consider you an [ __ ], then you really are
дети вас считают мудаком то вы реально
an [ __ ], let’s start a little in the
[__] это давайте начнем немножко в
fourteenth year from another
четырнадцатом году с другого
DPR LC They just wanted to peacefully peacefully
ДНР лнр Они просто хотели мирно мирно
where she watches Donetsk Show me Who
где она смотрит Донецке Покажите мне Кто
and when he created the DNS Who and when created the
и когда создал DNS Кто и когда создал
DPR when
ДНР когда
initially
изначально изначально Донецка
there was no Donetsk Donetsk Regional Council and Luhansk
нет Донецкий областной Совет и Луганские
Regional Council not the city council of
областной совет не городской совет
Donetsk did not make any decisions on the
Донецка не принимал никаких решений о
creation of the DPR Who created the DPR
создании ДНР Кто создал ДНР
I don’t know for sure Apparently
Я не знаю точно Видимо
they created it themselves when they are who
они сами создали когда они это кто
Well who is who
Ну кто кто
residents What
жители Какие
residents of Luhansk Donetsk Donetsk residents
жители Луганской Донецка Донецка жителей
million which of these residents in what
миллион кто из этих жителей в какой
way created this DPR And you go ask
способ создал этот ДНР А ты иди спроси у
them yourself So I ask you look
них сам Вот и вот я спрашиваю смотрите
You don’t you
Вы нет Вы
ask this now tell me again I
спрашиваете это вот скажите я еще раз
say the Donetsk Regional Council
говорю Донецкий областной Совет
elected in the topic by the deputies of Donetsk
избранный в теме депутатами Донецка
Donetsk region Lugansk Regional
Донецкой области Луганские областной
Council, expelled by all residents of the
Совет изгнанный всеми всеми жителями
Lugansk region, did not make any
Луганской области не принимали никаких
decisions on the creation of this Who if you
решений о создании данного Кто если вы
say that it was created by some
говорите что было создано какими-то
For example, I know that
Например я знаю что
Alexander Boroday Yes, he proclaimed himself
Александр бородай Да провозгласил себя
the first head of the Donetsk People's
первым главой Донецкой народной
Republic Yes, he
Республики
proclaimed himself the Minister of Defense of the
Да провозгласил себя министром обороны
Donetsk Republic Yes  none of the inhabitants of the
Донецкой Республики Да никто из жителей
Donetsk region proclaimed this
Донецкой области не провозглашал эту
Republic
Республику
when when
когда когда
at April April 2014 when
при Апрель Апрель 2014 года когда у вас
Otto began in you, not yet the
началось Отто уже не не ещё же
fourteenth year, April
четырнадцатого года вот апрель
of the fourteenth year they captured, see
четырнадцатого года захватили смотрите
the capture of Slavyansk Yes, and hostilities began
захват Славянска Да и начались военные
Here you look, for example
действия Вот вы смотрите например
Imagine what is there  a man
Представьте что есть вот там человеком
Alexander Vlasenko comes from
Александр Власенко приезжает из
St. Petersburg to Donetsk Yes, and I tell
санкт-петербурга в Донецк Да и говорит я
you with weapons and I say now I will be
тебе с оружием и говорит я теперь буду
the head of the Donetsk People's Republic from
главой Донецкой народной Республики из
various Russian militants Yes O people
боевиками разными российскими да О люди
who were against run away to Kiev in
которые были против убегают в Киев в
Kharkov Yes Who thinks that now it will all
Харьков Да Кто думает что сейчас это всё
end waiting  but it doesn’t end
закончится ждёт а оно не заканчивается
yes That is, you say that someone
Вот то есть вы утверждаете что кто-то
created the Donetsk People’s Republic there
там создал донецкую народную Республику
Who if for example I say wait
Кто если например я говорю подожди
he started who started again who Look
он начал кто начал еще раз кто Смотри
who created you run away from the topic let’s we
кто создал ты убегаешь с темы давай мы
drive you first therefore and then we
тебя повозим сначала поэтому а потом мы
drive you  here we are driving you in the face Otherwise,
тебя повозим вот мы тебя повозим мордой
first you will tell me Who created it and when If
А то сначала ты мне скажешь Кто и когда
you say that if you say
Если вы говорите что если ты говоришь
that it was created by people when, for
что её создали это люди когда вот
example, Ukraine Yes, look at the independence of
например Украину Да смотри независимость
Ukraine, the Supreme Council proclaimed the
Украины провозгласил Верховный Совет
Verkhovna Rada of Ukraine on August 20,
Верховная Рада Украины 20 четвёртого
1991, a body elected by all residents
1991 года орган избранный всеми жителями
Ukraine who If you are not I am Alexander
Украины кто Если ты нет Я тебя Александр
Vlasenko from St. Petersburg Everything ran away
Власенко из санкт-петербурга Всё убежал
like this some kind of water comes out that you
вот так выходит какой-то вода что это вы
don’t raise your children here in
своих детей не воспитывайте тут в
Ukraine I’m shorter with them for two years here
Украине я два года с ними короче тут
at all it’s nothing then they’ll put me in because it
вообще это ничего то меня посадят потому
’s right to do it because  what are you
что правильно делать потому что ты
Alexander [ __ ] You are sitting in St. Petersburg and
Александр [__] Ты сидишь в Питере да
ass on the couch Your country is killing
жопой на диване Твоя страна убивает
children in this my country in Ukraine and you
детей в этой моей стране в Украине и ты
start
начинаешь
asking questions why they are
задавать вопросы почему они тебя
sending you don’t you think why Your
посылают ты не думаешь почему Твоя
country is sending
страна посылает
soldiers here of these freaks Why is
воинов сюда своих этих уродов Почему
your country sending missiles here killing
твоя страна ракеты сюда посылает убивает
these children you wonder why they
этих детей ты удивляешься Почему они
hate me they will hate you for decades
меня ненавидят они тебя еще десятки лет
they will hate you Damn let's be
будут ненавидеть они тебя будут Блин
a star damn it where they only
давайте звездюлей блин где тебя только
see you understand in Germany in Turkey
увидят понимаешь в Германии в Турции
Because you are a bastard supporting people
Потому что ты [__] поддержку людей И
what is a knowledgeable
знаю чудо А что такое осведомлённый
kilogram right at a time autumn and the experience
килограмм прям за раз осень а опыт
[music]
[музыка]
YouTube driving us through Georgiev’s car into a
YouTube загоняя нас через кар Георгиев в
shadow ban and a rich look is not
теневый бан и дужебогатого вида не
shown to people in private,
показывается людям в частном на
information about streams is shown
показывается информация про стримы тому
in order to have a little operational zazok
для того чтобы мало оперативный зазок
Sign right at a time and try there in
Подпишите прям за раз а попыт там в
kilogram about Krim video
килограмме о Крим видео
information and we would have brought you attramats
информация и мы бы вынес вам аттраматы
in a stylish
по стильной
operational asterisks it’s not working Total
оперативный звездок не залажено Итого
type how do you like YouTube Glory to Ukraine
типа как вам YouTube Слава Украине